<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Ara 3D Blog</title>
        <description>Tech, Travel, and other Tails.</description>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
        <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 20:05:31 -0400</pubDate>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 20:05:31 -0400</lastBuildDate>
        <generator>Jekyll v4.4.1</generator>
        
            <item>
                <title>New Beginnings, Big Adventures (and a Few Other Tails Along the Way)</title>
                <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;hola&quot;&gt;Hola!&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m &lt;strong&gt;Anne B.&lt;/strong&gt;, the official HR Assistant to &lt;em&gt;The Real Boss&lt;/em&gt; (yes, the one with four legs and an endearing sense of entitlement). Sometimes, I work very closely with Christopher — even literally, when the boss feels generous with seating arrangements.
It’s my pleasure to be here for my very first blog post, and I couldn’t be more excited to start this journey with you.
In my role, you’ll usually find me working behind the scenes. When I’m not in the thick of HR or marketing magic, I make sure our workplace stays fun; after all, you can’t build a great company without a few laughs and the occasional pet-talk break.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;-throwback-travels&quot;&gt;🧳 Throwback Travels&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ll be sharing a special series called &lt;strong&gt;Throwback Travels&lt;/strong&gt;: stories from past trips, from tagging along with Christopher to AEC hackathons, symposiums, and other events, to discovering new corners of the world. 
While he does what he loves most (building new tech and connecting with brilliant minds), I get to soak in the sights, food, and culture along the way.
Expect some nice pics, travel tips (learned the hard way), and more than a few &lt;em&gt;“I can’t believe this just happened”&lt;/em&gt; moments.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Disclaimer:&lt;/strong&gt; Our trips always include at least one of those!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh, and did I mention I come from a small town in Cuba?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Imagine a girl whose idea of a traffic jam was a horse taking a break in the middle of the road, taking a taxi from the airport in New York or Paris, and praying she’d make it to the hotel alive!&lt;br /&gt;
But I digress.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;images/anne-bicycle.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Anne Bicycle&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;center&gt;*From the sandy roads of Santa Lucia (Cuba) to the cobbled paths along the Seine (Paris).*&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;images/life-is-journey.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Life is a Journey&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;center&gt;*Now enjoying the ride with Christopher!*&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stay tuned for these stories and more (including the quintessential trips to recharge and disconnect). And don’t worry: it won’t be all about travel. There will be plenty of other &lt;strong&gt;“tails”&lt;/strong&gt; along the way!
I’m thrilled to share all of this with you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Here’s to new beginnings, shared adventures, and yes, a few wrong turns&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(&lt;em&gt;because who doesn’t love a good detour?&lt;/em&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;– Anne B.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 11:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
                <link>http://localhost:4000/anne-intro</link>
                <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/anne-intro</guid>
                
                <category>introductions</category>
                
                
            </item>
        
            <item>
                <title>Meet the Real Boss (and How It All Began)</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Allo! I’m Bernie, the Real Boss at Ara 3D.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is my very first blog post, and as someone who takes posts seriously, I’m so excited!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;how-it-all-started&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How It All Started&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I joined the team in 2020 at just 8 weeks old. Inexperienced and still figuring out stairs? Sure. But they were desperate to fill the position.&lt;br /&gt;
And I had that leadership presence you just can’t train.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A few candidates were considered, but my CV stood out. (There was definitely some beauty bias involved.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The job offer was irresistible: open-air office, catered meals, VIP travel, chauffeur service, full medical coverage, spa services, and the unbeatable perks of 24/7 staff support and total respect. A dream package!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Long story short, I left the office I’d briefly shared with a loud miniature human and headed off to my new adventure. Woof!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;images/bernie/first-day.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Bernie&apos;s Puppy picture&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-ruff-beginnings&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Ruff Beginnings&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I won’t lie, though. The early days at Ara 3D were a bit &lt;em&gt;ruff&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;
The team expected me to follow their lead, even if I had been hired to lead them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They also wanted me to understand the office jargon on Day One. And sure, that was super easy. But I decided to pretend I didn’t understand words like “Drop” or “Come.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It took a bit of time (and a lot of patience) for them to accept it:&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;I am The Boss. I do not “Come.”&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Still TRUE (✔️).&lt;br /&gt;
Well… give me a treat, and I may.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;images/bernie/bernie-in-snow.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Bernie in the Snow&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;leading-by-example-and-by-leash&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Leading by Example (and by Leash)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another huge challenge was the walks, my top prescription for a happy mind and a productivity boost.&lt;br /&gt;
The team needed serious help. Having packed some extra Covid pounds, they had to be motivated to get back in shape.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was exhausting work. They walked slower than Cuban WiFi.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I had to pull them all the time, all while teaching them the finer things in life:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Smell the flowers&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Breathe in the breeze&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;(OK, maybe don’t eat the butterflies)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Greet everyone with &lt;em&gt;you-are-the-best-person-ever&lt;/em&gt; enthusiasm!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They have improved, but it’s still a work in progress.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!-- Use HTML for side-by-side images if needed --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;images/bernie/smell-the-flowers.png&quot; width=&quot;48%&quot; /&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;images/bernie/in-the-bushes.jpg&quot; width=&quot;48%&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;looking-back-with-tail-wags&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Looking Back (With Tail Wags)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Looking back, those early days were wild! So glad they believed in me and hired me to do what I do best:&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Boosting the team’s morale and building a culture where walkies, Zoom(ies), and vacations are always a priority.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Can’t wait to share more with you!&lt;br /&gt;
Put on your harness for more adventures and behind-the-scenes Ara 3D &lt;em&gt;tails&lt;/em&gt;, as we chase dreams (or balls!) and shake up the future of the AEC field.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hasta pronto, amigos!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;images/bernie/looking-back.png&quot; alt=&quot;Bernie looking back&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;- &lt;em&gt;Bernie, Real Boss / Real Cute&lt;/em&gt; 🐶&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 16:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
                <link>http://localhost:4000/real-boss</link>
                <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/real-boss</guid>
                
                <category>introductions</category>
                
                
            </item>
        
            <item>
                <title>Welcome to Tech, Travel, and other Tails</title>
                <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;welcome-to-the-official-ara-3d-team-blog&quot;&gt;Welcome to the official Ara 3D team blog.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Welcome to our team blog!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m Christopher Diggins, the founder of Ara 3D.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My blog on this site will be a little different from my previous forays into blogging (on sites like Artima.com, Dr. Dobb’s, Microsoft, O’Reilly, Autodesk Area).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As I’ve grown older, I’ve come to better appreciate the importance of storytelling - offering context for the explorations, creations, and learnings. It’s not just about facts and deliverables, it’s also about the human (or canine) journey behind them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So yes, I’ll still be posting technical deep-dives, lessons, and experimental findings. But I’ll also be sharing more personal stories: my inspirations, my adventures, and my interactions both with the two-legged kind and the four-legged kind-as a technologist,entrepreneur, maneuvering the complex world of neurotypicals for half a century.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This blog is a shared space. You’ll also be hearing from the Ara 3D team, our partners, our friends, and our guests.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’re building this as a living archive: a place for documenting our adventures, learnings, ideas, stories, and projects - written in a voice that’s uniquely ours.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks for being here. 🤗&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 11:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
                <link>http://localhost:4000/hello-world</link>
                <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/hello-world</guid>
                
                <category>introductions</category>
                
                
            </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>